Guide to the Les K. Wright papers and Bear History Project files, 1959-2010.
Wright, Les K. papers and Bear History Project files, 1959-2010
- Series II. Publications and Academic Work
  - Reviews
    - An inconvenient truth, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 101)
    - Paceful warrior, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 102)
    - Cavite, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 103)
    - Wah-Wah, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 104)
    - Galleon and other stories:the Saatchi Gallery, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 105)
    - Princely Splendor:The Dresden Court 1580-1620, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 106)
    - Eugenic design, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 107)
    - Secrets of Sant' Angelo (Box 50, Folder 108)
    - Reefer Madness:The movie musical, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 109)
    - Our fathers, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 110)
    - Secuestro Express, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 111)
    - The brothers Grimm, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 112)
    - Person of interest, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 113)
    - Guernsey, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 114)
    - Serenity, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 115)
    - Quality of life, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Grizzly Man, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - The Perfect Crime, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Margaret Cho:Assasin, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Dear Wendy, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - A sound of thunder, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Thumbsucker, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Taisho Chic, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Green Street Hooligans, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - The prize winner of Defiance, Ohio, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Wallace and Gromit in the curse of the were-rabbit, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Nine Lives, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Three...Extremes, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Derailed, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - German studies review, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 63)
  - Published and Unpublished Articles
    - Exempla- "Enier Alten Stimme Neuer Klang", 1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - What Happened to the Gay Struggle in German Federal Republic?- GBB 1:3, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Unfaehig Zur Emanzipation?- GBB 4, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - RFSL (Swedish Gay Liberation Group) & Gay Liberation in Sweden- GBB 5, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Review of Rumaker, Curzon, and Hall- GBB 7, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - The Graphic Work of Louis Corint, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Berlin Revisited, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - N. Gogol, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Moral Morality, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Kleist, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Personal Dispatches- Jay Preston- review, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Queer Pleasure/ Politics at Harvard, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Cruising the Personals, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Clinton, New York, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Gaiety Transformed- David Bergman and Gay Culture in America- G. Herdt- reviews, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - "Death Becomes Her" and "Enchanted April", 1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - We of the Third Sex- J. Jones, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Gay Genocide as Literary Trope, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - George Whitmore, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - All American Boy- Scott Peck, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - San Francisco, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Schwul is Paradoxical, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - San Francisco Encyclopedia of AIDS, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - A Huge (but relatively private) Hell, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Gay and Lesbian Biography, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - German, Jewish, Married, Gay, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - The Sociology of the Urban Bear, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Exploring the "Bear" Phenomena, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Gay Bears on the Prowl, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - In the Company of Bears, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Sex and Reciprocity, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Bears go for Each Other, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Movie Life: Scenes and Stars, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Bear Sex and Hero Worship, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - What is a Bear? Further Reflections, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Workshops from Bear Expo, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - The Man Next Door: Going Home Again, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Separated at Bearth, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - The Bear Facts- Cover Story, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Lurch Interview, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Bears! Where Did We Come From?, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Tracking Prehistoric Bears, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - The Original Bears Mailing List- written with S. Dyer, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - The Search: How I Found a Publisher, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Fitchburg, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Our Stories, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Committee on Lesbian and Gay History Newsletter, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Unpublished Manuscripts, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Universal Soldier, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Untying the Knots, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - The Hamiltonian Newsletter, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Bear Book Reviews, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Bear Book Cover Art, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Reviews- The Bear Book, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - The Bear Book Documents, 1995-97 (Box 4, Folder 16-17)
    - The Bear Book II Manuscript, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
    - The Bear Book II Manuscript, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 20-22)
    - Bear Icons 2, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Bear Book II Images Gallery, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 12-13)
    - Bear Book II Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 14-16)
    - Bear Book II: 19th Century Masculinities, Art, & Mass Culture, 1993,1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 17-18)
    - Les Wright Dossier, Binders 1-3, February 1999 (Box 20, Folder 21-23)
    - "1989: Still Hoping for a Dickensian Christmas!", 1989(?) (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - AIDS in Europe project, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - "Bears" Encyclopedia of LGBT History and Culture, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - "The Ecstasy of Terror", poetry book manuscript (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - "'Female' Trouble in Films", 1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - "From Anthropometry to Star: The NBCS in Theory and Practice", 2000 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - "Gay & Lesbian Development Issues", PSY 5309, John F. Kennedy University, instructed by Les Wright (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - "The Genius of Place" faculty grant application, 1996/1997 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - "Medicalizing the Enemy", 1989 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Misc. correspondence re: written works, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Misc. writing, articles (some by Les Wright) re: AIDS (?) (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Forward (by Les Wright) to More Bear Cookin', 2004 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - "Night of Shattered Dreams" research proposal, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Queer Masculinities special issue: Men & Masculinity, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 20-21)
    - Queer Masculinities special issue drafts for print, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Queer Masculinities Men & Masculinities guest editor for Michael Kimmel, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - "Rules of the Game" manuscript, first draft, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - "The Search: How I Found a Publisher for my First Book and What I Did Along the Way", 1997 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - "Virology of 'Degeneration'" (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Chronicle of Higher Education: State of Research & Professors, 1996-1998 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Fire Houses of Gay Literature: Post-Stonewall Literary Essays (and various academic conferences)(?) (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Massachusetts Task Force on Sexual Assault & Abuse, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Task Force on Sexual Assault and Abuse, testimony by Wright to Gov. Jane Swift, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - UCB (University of California Berkeley) Gay Studies (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Stonewall Library lecture on BHP, Fort Lauderdale, June 13, 2003 (Box 26)
    - "New Gay Capital" visit, Fort Lauderdale, April 2003 (Box 26)
    - "Tangled Memories of a Wounded Storyteller: Notes on Bear History and Cultural Memory," manuscript, 2005 (Box 26)
    - Response to manuscript "Understanding the Bear Movement in Gay Male Culture: Redefining Masculinity", 2005 (Box 26)
    - NashobaBear, Live Journal, March 2004 - April 2005; 14 folders (Box 31)
    - "Whitman's Leaves of Grass at 150", 2005 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - "Bear Essentials: A Different Kind of Gay Identity" in Voice Male, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - "I Used to Have AIDS", 2004 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - "Bear Vocabulary" in Out, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - "Whatever happened to the Gay struggle in the German Federal Republic" in Gay Books Bulletin, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - "Unfaellig Zur Emancipation?Homosexuelle Zwischen Getto und Brefreiung:Enire Untersuchung Zur Stagnation Der Homosexuellebewegung" in Gay Books Bulletin, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - "The RFSL and Gay liberation in Sweden" in Gay Books Bulletin, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - International Gay Philatelic Journal, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - "The truth as social construction:A textbook example" in Out in Academia, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - "Homosexual Psyches in Wilhelminian Germany" in Gay Studies Newsletter, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - "The Sociology of the Urban Bear" in Drummer, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - "Queer pleasure / Politics at Harvard" in San Francisco Sentinel, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - "Gay Bears on the prowl" in San Francisco Sentinel, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - "Exploring the "Bear" phenomena " in Seattle Gay News, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - San Francisco Sentinel, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Bear, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - "Movie Reviews","In the company of Bears","Sex and the inmutable Laws of reciprocity","Bear sex and Hero workship" in The Bear Fax (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - "Bears go for each other","What is a Bear?Further reflections","Those astounding whorshops from Bear Expo '92","Bearskin bend lodge journal" in The Bear Fax, 1991-1993 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - "Letters to Editor" in Lesbian and Gay Studies Newsletter, 1992-1998 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Bay Areas Editor's Forum, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Lambda Philatelic Journal, 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - "Germany:Schwul is Paradoxical","Yet Another Way Out:Scott Pecks All American Boy" in The Harvard Gay and Lesbian Review, 1995-1996 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - "Separated at Bearth? San Francisco vs.Boston" in The New England Bear, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - "The Bear Facts" in San Francisco Frontiers Magazine, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - "Bear Community Icon and Comic" ,"The Original Bears Mailing List and Interview with Steve Dyer" in American Bear, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - "Sociology of a Bear","The Bear Book:Reading in the History and Evolution of a Gay male subculture" in Classic Bear, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - "How I found a publisher for my first book and what I did along the way" in The Publishing Triangle News, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - The Harvard Gay and Lesbian Review, 1997-1998 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - "From outsider to insider:queer politics in German film,1970-94" in European Journal of Cultural Studies, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - "Testimony Statement to Massachusetts Governor's Task Force on Sexual Assault and Abuse" in Men Speak Out, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - "Men and Health:The "Forgotten Generation" of people with Aids","The Soul Beneath the skin by David Nianmons Reviewed in Voice Male, 1999-2007 (Box 51, Folder 40-43)
    - "Surviving childhood sexual assault" in Mokan Plus!, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - "Reflections on Safer Sex" in Crosspoints, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - "Berlin revisited Jewel on the Spree" in San Francisco Review of Books (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - "We're everywhere now","Bears:the birth (a reflection)","The wired network:Bears in the 1990s","Commercialized tribalism:Bears in the 2000s" in Bear Track, 2006-2007 (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - "On Bear Spirit","Bear Spirit" in White Crane, 2007-2008 (Box 51, Folder 48)
    - "Bears in the begining","The 1990s.The emergence of an International Bear Community","The New Millenium:Bears and commercialized tribalism" in A Bear's Life, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 49)
    - "A History of Bear Pride","The Original Bears Mailing List" in A Bear's Life, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 50)
    - "From Local to Global:the rise of the international Bear circuit","Bear Spirit:New Beginnings","Falling in Love:Differentiating sexual desire and real intimacy","The Sex and Intimacy Continuum" in A Bear's Life, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 51-52)
    - The San Francisco Bay Area Gay and Lesbian Historical Society, 1985-1990 (Box 51, Folder 56)
    - The Committee on Gay and Lesbian History, 1996-2000 (Box 51, Folder 57-58)
    - The Gay and Lesbian Historical Society of Northern California, 1990-1992 (Box 51, Folder 59)
    - Phoenix, 1972-1974 (Box 51, Folder 60)
    - Exempla, 1975-1977 (Box 51, Folder 61)
    - Exempla, 1977-1978 (Box 51, Folder 62)
    - Byzantium, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Point Blank, 1995-1997 (Box 52, Folder 2-3)
    - Tonquere, Men and Masculinities, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Mount Ida College Magazine (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Loose letters in magazines (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Articles about Les Wright (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Miscellany:Frameline 33 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Poems (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Papers (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Gay Bears! Oral History Project:Interview (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Interview for Dissertation Research (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Miscellany:NGITF, Hospice Foundation of America (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Slides (Box 52, Folder 14-17)
    - Slides' Guide (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Encyclopedia of Aids (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Poppers!Rimming!Tittentrimm! (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Tapes and Cd, Tr 8669a-Tr 8670a-Cd 738 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - From outsider to insider: queer politics in German film,1970-94, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Academic Courses
    - Russian 130, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Russian 140 (Box 26)
    - Russian 226: Modernism, 1989 (Box 26)
    - Schwule Belletristik (proposed) (Box 26)
    - German 120, 1989 (Box 26)
    - German 220 (Die Novelle), 1988 (Box 26)
    - Comparative Literature, 1985, 1988 (Box 26)
    - German 218B: Weimar, K.L. Mann, 1988 (Box 26)
    - English 099, Summer 2001 (Box 26)
    - English 101, 1994-2003 (Box 26)
    - English 102, 1993-2003 (Box 26)
    - English 130A: The Literature of Addiction and Dysfunction, Fall 1993 (Box 26)
    - English 230: Drama, 2000 (Box 26)
    - English 320: The Novel, Fall 1996 (Box 26)
    - SL 401: Self and Society, 1998 (Box 26)
    - Application: Instructor of Gay and Lesbian Studies at the City College of San Francisco, 2004-2005 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Tenure Manuscript
    - Tangled Memories of a Wounded Storyteller, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Series III. Correspondence
  - Abdulkadir, Mariza, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Abicht, Ludo, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Academic contacts, 1989-1998 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Adams, John D., 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Aiken, Skip, 1988-1992 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Alexander, John, 1991-1999 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Alguire, Brian, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Anderson, Dennis, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 31-32)
  - Aul, Billie, 1972-2000 (Box 4, Folder 33-36)
  - Babu, Shoury, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Barnard, Sylvia, 1988-1997 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Barrick, Bill, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Beghtol, Larry, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Benzow, Greg, 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Berube, Allen, 1985-1996 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Bergman, David, 1992-1996 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Bergthold, Milt (Frank), 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Blanchard, Dennis, 1987-2000 (Box 4, Folder 45-48)
  - Boletta, Bill, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Borden, Gene, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Bourque, Jeff, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Bredigkeit, Helmut, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Broerman, Bruce, 1989-1999 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Bronski, Michael, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Brylawski, Ellen, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Bulger, Richard, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Cheney, Wayne, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Chester, Mark (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Chohan, Sabir, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cibuls, Juris, 1991-2000 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Clark, Jason, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Clements, Clancy, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - CLGH- Committee on Lesbian and Gay History, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Colfer, Paul, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Comeau, Gary, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Compton, Dennis, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Conroy, Stuart, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Cornwall, Heather, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Cheech, Dennis, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Crew, Louie, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Crimmins, Barry, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Cromey, Robert Warren, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Croxton, Bill, 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Dahl, Mel "CYA" (Bear Magazine), 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Dalip, 1988-1992 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Davis, Joel, 1990-1999 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - De Cecco, John, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Dellamora, Richard, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - De La Rosa, Vic, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Demey, Pierre, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Dickeman, Millie, 1991-2000 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Donnellan, Brendan, 1988-1999 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Drew, Jim, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Dynes, Wayne, 1982-1996 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Eissler, Wilfried, 1981-1993 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Emery, Mike, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Ermolaev, Gennadij, 1981-1994 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Evans, Peter and Herzog, Mark, 1994-1999 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Finkemeier, Thornsten, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Fonce-Zimmerman, Yonah, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Francis, Bob, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Freeberg, Bill, 1992-1997 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Fritscher, Jack, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Ganczaruk, Sam and Ed Orrick, 1992-2000 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Ganczaruk, Sam, 1992-2000 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Gardiner- Scott, Tanya, 1990-2000 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Gavin, Terry, 1985-1990 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Gerard, Dave, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Gerbracht, Bob, 1992-1998 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Gescher, Gwen, 1976-1999 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Gesell, Bob, 1990-1998 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Gilgun, John, 1988-2000 (Box 5, Folder 46-49)
  - GLHSNC-SFBAGLHS, 1988-1995 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Goodall, Jack and Jim Yarborough, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Goodman, Simon, 1989-1999 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Grady, Tom, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Gustafson, Laura, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Hallberg, Georg, 1979-1999 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Harper, Nildo, 1984-1997 (Box 5, Folder 56-57)
  - Hazel, Dann, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Hekma, Gert, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Heller, Jonathan, 1988-2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Henne, Sidi, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Herzer, Manfred, 1988-1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Hes-Luttich, Ernest, 1991-1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Higgs, David, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Hill, Scott, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hirshberg, Bob, and John Craig, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Holmes, Tim, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Huebner, Chris, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Iremonger, Rich, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Jaffe, Dan, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Jayasundara, Pinisiri, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Jochum, Astrid, 1974-1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, Mark Scott, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Jones, Jim, 1989-2000 (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
  - Karlinsky, Simon, 1988-1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Kasirer, Meir, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Kaufman, Brian and Martin Swinger, 1994-1999 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Keating, Mike, 1983-1991 (Box 6, Folder 21-23)
  - Kennedy, Hubert, 1988-2000 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Kern, Doug and Aileen, 1972-1991 (Box 6, Folder 25-26)
  - Kirkby-MacLean, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Klein (Marga and Lumbed), 1982-1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Klein, Steve, 1989-2000 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Krunke, Hans, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Kumar, Vijay, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - La Greca, Scott, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Lassell, Michael, 1981-1995 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Lattey, Elsa, 1988-1999 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Lawrence, Carl, 1993-2000 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Lazere, Arthur, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Lech, Patty, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Lehmann, Ruth, 1977-1993 (Box 6, Folder 38-39)
  - Leita, Francesa, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Letters to Editors, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Libby, Tom, 1993-2010 (Box 6, Folder 42-43)
  - Lynch, Michael, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - MacIlwain, Bob, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 45-48)
  - Maguire, Greg, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Manaday, Wes, 1990-1996 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Martin, Jim, 1994-2000, undated (Box 6, Folder 51-52)
  - Mass, Larry D., 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Maverman, Luke, 1993-2000 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - McCawn, Tommy, 1994-1999 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - McCloskey, Danny, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Van Der Meer, Theo, 1986-1995 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Mendes-Leite, Rommel, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Miller, Bob, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Miller, Russ, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Mitchell, Gary (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Nelson, Emmanuel, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Newman, Hans-Peter, 1986-1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Noakes, Derek, 1979-1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Norris, TJ, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 4-9)
  - O'Jesjo, Leif and Altenbvchner, Josef, 1993-2000 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - O'Higgins, Patrick and Jeryl Neher, 1994-1997 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Outcalt, John, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Palmer, Bill, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Pate, Larry, 1989-2000 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Paton, Jim, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Penn, Lee, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Piel, Barb, 1994-1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Pioli, Rob, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Policarpio, Joe, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Pollock, Ken, 1988-2000 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Posten, Joel, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Preston, John, 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Price, Tony, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Ratcliffe, Ken, 1982-1992 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Reams, Larry, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Relac, Mike, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Rhine, Dont, 1996-2000 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Rindar, Kjell, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Robbins, Philip, 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Rotes, Eric, 1989-2000 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Roth, Mike, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Sahin, Mali, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Salmon, Larry, 1979-1984 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - San Francisco, Sunory, 1992-2000 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - San Francisco Trip, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Scarberry, Bob, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Schmidt, Michael (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Schneider, Richard, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Schultz, Ilona, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Schwartz, Jurgen, 1971-1994 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Seeger, Joe, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Shanton, George, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Shawn, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Sibal, Jim, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Silver, Roger, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Singer, Joseph, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Smith, Nigel, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Stewart, Charles, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Stonekey, Sharon, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Stucts, Eric, 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Suresha, Ron, 1994-2000 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Sweet, Denis, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Taylor, Buzz (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Thompson, Dave and Thomm Paddeh, 1996-2000 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Tobin, Mike, 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Topping, John, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Townsend, Robin, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Turner, Gary, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Vadon, Bud, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Vasquez, Louis, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Verdun, David, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Vollmer, T., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Wahl, Bill, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Wallace, Keith, 1968-1975 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)